Anh Quan Ly

Retail Senior Executive/Sony Center Management | Male | 20/01/1988



Experience 9 years

Latest company Sony Electronics Vietnam as Retail Senior

Executive/Sony Center Management

Highest education Masters

Languages English - Advanced | French - Intermediate

Email **lyanhquan201@gmail.com**

Phone **0989172331**

Address No 13, 42 Street, Tân Quy ward, Distr.7,

District 7, Ho Chi Minh City

SUMMARY

I have rich knowledge, experiences on Retail Channel Management, Marketing and Service Management. Further, in-depth Online Sales Management is a big plus. Besides, I was professionally trained, and worked in international environments, combine with wide range work skills and EQ over IQ. My only purpose is to dedicate and contribute to every organization. My shorterm odjective is to reach the Management Level Position. I'm a quick learner, and easy to adapt in various conditions, business field.

*Added info: I have passion in books, cars, education, kids services. Further, I'm an individual real estate investor, since 2011.

SKILL



- Marketing
- Problem Solving
- Customer Service
- B2C Sales
- Consulting
- Leadership
- Sales Electronics Products
- Sales Planning
- Retail Management
- Ecommerce Background

WORK EXPERIENCE

04/2014 - 12/2019

Retail Senior Executive/Sony Center Management

Sony Electronics Vietnam

*Main Missions:

1- Retail & Operation Supervise:

- Manage team, include 19 Store Managers of the Sony Center Specialized Chain Store
- Plan & execute store's services for end-user: extended waranty, 0% installment, Membership program....
- Supervise Store Managers to ensure daily operation standard: product display, promotion implementation, staff attitude, inventory, service offers...
- Business planning in order to improve sales, attract customer
 their satisfaction.
- Plan & implement training to store's staff: Selling skill, Product knowledge and Store operation standard.



- Timely review, analyze data to define issues, then come up with improvement plan and execution.
- Work with various partners to deploy consumer added services: Grab, VP Bank, Momo, Payoo....

2- Advertising & Promotion Management:

- Supervise team to deploy Digital Marketing Campaign & Promotions frequently, apply for both online and offline stores.
- Collaborate with Marketing & Sales division for promotion campaigns, ensure sales target & stores performance.
- Control & evaluate campaigns performance, KPIs, ROI in order to optimize execution plan and budget.

3- E-commerce Management:

- Work as project manager to buil first e-commerce platform for Sony Center chain store (sonycenter.vn)
- Supervise daily sales operation: transaction, inventory control, online payment, delivery partners.... in order to reach target
- Supervise online content: product info, price, news, eservices....
- Digital Marketing planning and ensure performance achieved: SEM, SEO, FB ads, E-news letter,....
- Manage platform functions & partners: Online Payment (OnePay), 0% Installment (Nganluong.vn), COD (GHN.vn, Boxme,...), e-survey....
- Planning & implement various promotions to enhance online sales performance, attract customer traffic to stores.
- Cross functional collaboration: IT, Marketing, Sales, Logistic,... to ensure smooth performance.
- Work closely with Web Developper to make sure the best performance, UX & UI, upgrades...



- Deploy Sony Center Mobile Application
- Manage budget for effectiviness and efficiency.

*Achievement:

- Become the pionner of Sony VN to implement the first ecommerce platform for Sony Center chain store. Avg revenue ~2 bil vnd/month.
- 2. Manage team to ensure unified store standard & services
- 3. Indepth experience in Retail, and E-commerce Management, Digital Marketing, Customer service and platform operation
- 4. Mastering skills: Communication, Leadership, Team work, Problem Solving, Customer-centric mindset, Stress & Time Management.

04/2013 - 04/2014

Sale Representative

Sony Electronics Vietnam

1- Business Development Role:

- Manage key dealers for the Sony Center chain store: Höng Nhân, Tân Tân
- Manage daily sales activities to ensure Sales target monthly/quartely/yearly.
- Ensure & support dealer for sales performance, follow daily/monthly progress, make sure reaching Sell Out achievement by dealer.
- Monitor & guide dealers to improve dealer performance, including sales, SKU planning, display standard,....
- Control inventory, daily supply, overdue payment,....in order to optimize dealer's profit
- Analyze sales data, copetitor's situation,....in order improve sales performance.



2- Operations supervise & control:

- Collaborate with related parties/departments: Marketing, Logistic, Accounting,... to ensure new product launching plan, sales trend, stock control, payment,....
- Supervise Store Manager to ensure: promotions implementation, display guideline, VMD, store standards....
- Analyze data, prepare improvement plan/reports in order to enhance performance.
- Strategic consult to managers on "Why and how" to improve business and satisfy dealer.

11/2011 - 03/2013

Sony Center Store Manager

Sony Electronics Vietnam

*MAIN MISSION

1- Supervise Store Sales Operation:

- Ensure reaching sales target monthly, quarterly, yearly.
- Daily supervise sales operations: inventory, customer interaction, store standard, problem solving...
- Manage staffs and make sure best customer experience was properly delivered.
- Manage all realated task to ensure Sony standard, product display, customer experience and satisfaction.
- Analyze sales data, customer perception in order for improvement actions.

2- Store Image Management:

- Ensure product display following Sony's highest standard, SKU planning & control, Touch & Try availability for consumers.
- Make sure all marketing & promotion campaigns were well



implemented, including POSM, VMD, Gift,....

• Monitor and plan for store renovation, fixing to meet Sony's guideline.

3- Store Activity Planning & Execution:

- Plan & conduct frequent trainings for staff: product knowledge, selling skills, store standard....
- Organize workshops, event at store to end-user to improve customer traffic and sales performance.

* ACHIEVEMENTS

- 1. First Store Manager in-charge of 3 consecutive new Sony Centers opening, including: Sony Center Crescent (Nov 2011), Nguyen Thi Minh Khai (Aug 2012) and Vincom A (Oct 2012)
- 2. Contribute significantly Sony Center's performance, including: sales revenue, product display, activities, staff's ability, and customer satisfaction.
- 3. Be promoted to higher post as Sale Representative on Apr 2013

04/2011 - 09/2011

Marketing Management Trainee

Kinderworld Education Group (Singapore International School)

*Main Mission:

- Participate & support in Marketing activities including: events, ads & media planning, marketing campaigns.
- Working closely with other departments: design, project, supplier,... for every marketing campaigns.
- Assigned to work as enrolment at SIS school Trung Son.

* Achievements:



- Successful events: Education Fair 2011 at Phu Tho Stadium,
 Grand Opening Day for SIS School Vung Tau,...
- Skills improvement: English, communication, team work, planning, customer-centric mind-set

EDUCATION

10/2016 - 07/2018

Master in Marketing, Sales and Services

Masters - CFVG HCMC (Paris Sorbonne University, ESCP Europe/France)

- -Obtained outstanding experiences in modern business context, globale vision, as well networking
- -Great improvement in strategic mindset, knowledge and management skills.
- -Nominated as Best student, MMSS11, intake 2016-2018

09/2007 - 08/2010

Business Administration

Bachelors - University Toulouse 1 Capitol, France

- Good study record, especially in Management, Marketing, Sales, Communication, appreciated by University's Professors.
- Completed Intership report and highly evaluated by University professors and the company
- Participate in various activities, such as charity, non-profit org, community support,...



REFERENCE

Mr.Phan Nhật Khôi

Retail Marketing & Training Supervisor at Sony Electronics VN khoi.phan@sony.com | 0903155146

